export default {
  // kanji
  "RI1l+KhkjzALidLZpsxIc8QU4T4HCQ==": { id: "RI1l+KhkjzALidLZpsxIc8QU4T4HCQ==", sid: "kanji", front: "K", back: "OY", hint: "MM" },
  "FUZn2mO9nXuBlnonaW12m6ey3oWdpQ==": { id: "FUZn2mO9nXuBlnonaW12m6ey3oWdpQ==", sid: "kanji", front: "K", back: "KY", hint: "MM" },
  "9VrXesm1JWVJRQwc8v+hlSKzdhc2YQ==": { id: "9VrXesm1JWVJRQwc8v+hlSKzdhc2YQ==", sid: "kanji", front: "K", back: "M", hint: "MM" },
  "x3z+FOfkhzNPcf0xXEJRE6H52R1SZA==": { id: "x3z+FOfkhzNPcf0xXEJRE6H52R1SZA==", sid: "kanji", front: "OY", back: "K", hint: "MM" },
  "h9got83aJoNu8lP1LxCBxllRj/GA6Q==": { id: "h9got83aJoNu8lP1LxCBxllRj/GA6Q==", sid: "kanji", front: "OY", back: "M", hint: "MM" },
  "tx/kwtNVqHCZ2Pcthk4GP4XJE1i3rg==": { id: "tx/kwtNVqHCZ2Pcthk4GP4XJE1i3rg==", sid: "kanji", front: "KY", back: "K", hint: "MM" },
  "4H3YRWuQZAUx3OHg2H+TZD4xjcng+A==": { id: "4H3YRWuQZAUx3OHg2H+TZD4xjcng+A==", sid: "kanji", front: "KY", back: "M", hint: "MM" },
  "AhWk48S4jgEWVTgK9NjVryhIFzTvuQ==": { id: "AhWk48S4jgEWVTgK9NjVryhIFzTvuQ==", sid: "kanji", front: "M", back: "K", hint: "MM" },
  "V84fd78G/roC1ZaGu0MfAAiWNr9siQ==": { id: "V84fd78G/roC1ZaGu0MfAAiWNr9siQ==", sid: "kanji", front: "M", back: "OY", hint: "MM" },
  "ZeAa+o5CZI9/6TP50Rk0Xgj0A7l2jA==": { id: "ZeAa+o5CZI9/6TP50Rk0Xgj0A7l2jA==", sid: "kanji", front: "M", back: "KY", hint: "MM" },
  // vocab
  "3UNJQV1ZhNMhiodJHR9RUzcJrIYKAg==": { id: "3UNJQV1ZhNMhiodJHR9RUzcJrIYKAg==", sid: "vocab", front: "V", back: "R" },
  "JWaBtSN/LhH2FY9OtNEUGhtzlrbSkg==": { id: "JWaBtSN/LhH2FY9OtNEUGhtzlrbSkg==", sid: "vocab", front: "V", back: "M" },
  "XgJBDHSMuPmtu3cIccMGTNLHQ+1YiQ==": { id: "XgJBDHSMuPmtu3cIccMGTNLHQ+1YiQ==", sid: "vocab", front: "R", back: "V" },
  "aHaaBZn7/QudfhNPOIh4HpWXpMsmqw==": { id: "aHaaBZn7/QudfhNPOIh4HpWXpMsmqw==", sid: "vocab", front: "R", back: "M" },
  "Rrh0lq/wRfXLXR2N6TvrFH8b2ZKCYA==": { id: "Rrh0lq/wRfXLXR2N6TvrFH8b2ZKCYA==", sid: "vocab", front: "M", back: "V" },
  "ay0jJE81SFepPQHvlTavSmYTnP4MrQ==": { id: "ay0jJE81SFepPQHvlTavSmYTnP4MrQ==", sid: "vocab", front: "M", back: "R" },
  // radicals
  "+xuV0JqxtKCxeVJMQT4f/w4vCbO/5Q==": { id: "+xuV0JqxtKCxeVJMQT4f/w4vCbO/5Q==", sid: "radicals", front: "R", back: "M" },
  "KWM2Kt8EjnwN3jeJGdWfQ/iIIhvBBQ==": { id: "KWM2Kt8EjnwN3jeJGdWfQ/iIIhvBBQ==", sid: "radicals", front: "M", back: "R" },
}
